[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'хоббі' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "趣味"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'готівка' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "現金"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'щоденник' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "日記"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'збирати, колекціонувати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "集めます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'грати (на струнних та клавішних інструментах)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "弾きます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'прати, мити' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "洗います"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'співати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "歌います"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'обмінювати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "換えます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'водити (машину)' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "運転します"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Передбачити, прогнозувати' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "予測します"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відвідувати, оглядати, йти на екскурсію,практику' read in kanji?",
        "answer": "見学します"
    }
]